The Bauer Kingdom,
bordered on the west by Sus and
on the east by the Noor Empire,
which remains a threat to this day.
Powerful families within the kingdom's
bounds rose to prominence over the years.
They became today's royals and nobles,
taxing commoners in their
bid to maintain peace.
However, the rise of magic blurred divisions
of power, threatening the status quo.
Because King LaSalle
believes in meritocracy,
he began admitting commoners to
the Royal Academy on scholarship.
Everyone would be treated
equally, or so he thought.
Don't call you fly yard.
What you want, say na inside yo!
Oh I want only you.
Don't When a children come in your foot.
Remember your as to think down.
I don't mind how happy ends.
Not real Son of God.
Written to bouff Scout.
A full - nostalgia.
Brian Chambers.
I call you upon you.
Ey you're good.
Once from emoإ.
Let's happen125.
You'll have to lose.
I can't believe.
Buppy.
It ain't gonna lie.
Kind but I won't. As long
as the feeling starts.
Let's wreak your heart.
So let's lift into a learned Henri.
Go.
Thanks for coming. Just.
Come on.
Shine your heart. Jackets. Say.
Let's lift.
You'll have to be? One side!
Rei Zhang Han!
More once!
It's a good world!
I don't want to give up
until you think about it!
It's fun!
I love you!
Commoner movement he
shouldn't have assaulted
him with magic I don't
know exactly what happened
but No one deserves that
most likely the commoner
said something offensive
to provoke the attack
Their little faction it's called the
commoner movement isn't it they were spewing
nonsense About nobles
and commoners being equal
foolish claims with no
basis in reality and
look what They led to it's no wonder they
say the tongue is the whip of evil you say
that but what would You think if a noble
spoke out and got hurt
a noble hypothetically
of course but not hypothetically You can
whip me evilly anytime this is the only
reality she knows guess
I can't blame her for
not Getting it um pardon me
we've completed his treatment
hello
again Matt right
Taylor I hate To do
this to you while you're
recovering but the
Academy Knights have some
questions I'm sure you
You must be in pain,
but do you think you could answer a few?
I refuse.
Everyone knows the knights are
those disgusting nobles lapdogs,
and I have absolutely
nothing to say to a commoner
who pledges her loyalty
to the likes of them.
Listen, Matt.
The knights are here to
protect all students.
And, well, cooperating would be wise.
We're commoners just like you.
We know how hard it is to redeem
yourself after crossing a noble.
And why is that?
Why is it a risk for us
to voice our opinions?
This is why we need to fight!
Try to relax, okay?
We're here to get your side of the story
and make sure you're treated fairly.
So please, Matt, just tell me
what happened out there today.
It started when me and some
others approached Prince Yu.
He honestly listened
to what we had to say.
But then that jerk found out about it.
You there, commoner,
stay away from Prince Yu!
I was livid, and I couldn't help myself.
I told them what I really thought.
I said that royals and nobles were
nothing but tax-leeching parasites.
What did you just say?
Please just stay calm, Miss Claire.
It's important that we
hear what he has to say.
It wasn't about me.
I couldn't stand him speaking out of you.
So, without even thinking, I took
out my wand to defend your honor.
What did you say?
Insolent mongrel, you shut your
mouth or I'll shut it for you!
And the next thing I knew,
I was waking up here.
Dammit.
Who do these nobles think they are?
One of them burned me alive because I took
a stand on something he disagreed with.
I was just trying to scare him.
I had no intention of using magic.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
I swear in the name of God.
His wand, where is it?
It's already been confiscated
and sent off for analysis.
I'll also be inspecting it soon.
That innocent boy could
have been any one of us.
We won't stand for this oppression!
We will continue to fight for equality.
We demand justice for our
brother and safety for all!
Word travels fast.
Even people who don't go to
school here are up in arms.
Hey, you mind explaining?
To us what you were doing with
this matt guy in the first place.
He wanted to speak to me
about His group's objective.
He asked me to listen.
Which was only fair.
But I never agreed to support their Cause.
Whether you did or not, that
was a pretty careless move. You.
You need to consider your
Position in this kingdom.
Before god, all are equal.
So we are taught a tenant
of the spiritual church.
I assume the church opens its
doors to anyone who knocks.
It would have been wrong of me to turn
that boy away without hearing him out.
On the subject of the
church, let's talk about the
lineage of the Bauer family.
Prince Rod and Prince Thane are the
sons of a princess from the land of
the Alps.
She was the former queen
and died at a young age.
Prince Yu's mother, Grishe,
is the current queen.
Before she married the king, she was
a cardinal of the spiritual church,
hence her son's scripture reciting.
The church is the dominant religion here,
and it centers around
devotion to the spirits.
The kingdom hoped that the marriage
would give it power over the church,
but that didn't happen.
Instead,
the church grew even more powerful thanks
to its connection to the royal family.
Prince Yu is often seen as a symbol of
the church's authority over the kingdom.
The teachings of the church tend to align
most with the commoner movement's beliefs.
I've even heard rumors floating around
that the church is financing them.
My guess is Matt and his friends approached
Prince Yu in hopes of requesting aid.
I'll admit that meeting
with them was irresponsible,
but Deed would never
hurt anyone on purpose!
I'd stake my life on it!
Apparently Deed's defense is
that he lost control of his wand,
and the magic discharged on its own.
Were any defects found in the wand?
I personally examined it
while keeping that in mind,
but I saw no signs that
it had malfunctioned.
If someone who knows magic tools as
well as you says so, it must be true.
Honestly, whatever occurs outside
the academy is beyond our control.
Let's stay focused on what we can
do until Deed's fate is determined!
The three of us can chat
with the noble students.
Hopefully something will get through?
Rey and Misha, you handle the commoners.
Listen to their grievances
and try to calm things down.
You don't seem too pleased
to have been given that task.
Cause I'm not.
I suck at talking to people
about serious stuff like this.
Although a head pat from you
might make me feel better. A what?
You want me to do my best try?
Do it, Claire.
You can do it, I believe in you.
Could you add a pinch of
love, like a tiny peach?
No! No!
No! That's not!
Let's get to work, people.
We've got a campus to quiet
down, and not much time to do it.
Yeah!
Oh, it's too crowded in here!
Of course it's crowded.
The sentence is about to be posted.
We all want to know what'll happen.
Oh, there he is.
What? No.
That can't be right.
Dean Murray is sentenced to be
under house arrest for one week?
That's it?
They've lost their minds!
A week of house arrest?
You're kidding!
He almost killed someone!
What kind of justice is that?
Miss Claire!
Nobody shouldn't be here right now.
Why?
Someone has to calm this chaos.
Come on, where are we going?
Quickly, this way.
It keeps getting worse.
What's going to happen now?
What happened to your meritocracy?
Isn't everyone supposed to
be equal at the Academy?
Nothing has changed and nothing ever will.
The nobles will always come out on top.
Entry into the Academy is prohibited.
Get back, all of you!
The Academy will be on temporary lockdown.
And the military will join our
guards until the protests end.
I will not stay quiet about this.
It's not enough.
That boy can't stand up to walk.
And yet, his attacker's
punishment is to stay at home?
Trust me, everyone here
feels the same way you do.
But it appears that some nobles
who disagree with the commoner
movement sought a reduced sentence
and got what they requested.
I thought they'd been
awfully quiet lately.
We let this happen right
under our noses. There's more.
Turns out the church is giving
its support to the nobles.
But that doesn't make any sense.
The church has been financing the
commoner movement, haven't they?
That's a political move, I'm sure.
They may claim that they never get involved
in politics, but that's obviously a lie.
Power struggles as usual.
They want to take public
support from the royal family.
They help both commoners and
nobles in order to heighten the
tension between them and weaken
the authority of the kingdom.
You.
Does Queen Rishay know about this?
Who can say?
I am not privy to my mother's
thoughts on the matter.
Why not?
Can't you just go talk to her?
I requested a meeting, but she refused.
I suppose that's her right as queen.
Yes, but she's your
mother first, isn't she?
What exactly are you implying?
It was a simple question.
Being her son does not
give me any power in this!
Pardon me.
I wonder if this is what
the church is truly after.
Think about it.
Perhaps they're trying to create
a rift between the princes.
Perhaps so.
Having us at odds would
undermine royal authority.
I think you may be onto something, Claire.
Fortunately, the military will be
protecting us from outside the gate.
But it's our job as knights to protect
the school grounds from within.
Miss Claire?
Yes? What is it?
Once you make it back to your room, I need
you to stay there until tomorrow morning.
What?
How can you ask something like that
with everything that's happening?
It's the Academy Knight's job to be
on call at a time like this, isn't it?
So you're saying you won't do as I ask?
Of course I won't.
I understand.
Then you leave me no choice.
Miss Claire!
What have you done to her?
It's alright.
I just put her to sleep with magic.
Now please, escort her to the
dorm and hide there until morning.
Promise you won't leave the
room no matter what happens.
Tonight, the protesters will
break down the school gate
What?
Wait, you know something, don't you?
Tell me what's going on Lene,
you love Miss Claire, right?
Why would you ever doubt that?
I've been in her service for
much longer than you have
Good, then I'll leave her to you.
I'm trusting you to do the right thing!
Ray, wait.
The soldiers just went down, not sure
what happened, but this is our chance?
Captain!
The protestors have reached the gate!
Cooperate with the military
and try to quiet the mob!
We must protect the
academy no matter the cost!
Where are the doors?
That noble is gonna get
what's coming to him!
Stop right there! Huh?
This is an order from your future king!
Do not take a single step closer!
What you're wasting time
I destroyed that bell
of yours now you have no
way to control monsters?
It was a clever invention but you'll
never get to use it Master Lambert
Hold on. Ray Taylor?
How did...
What are you doing here?
Stopping you before it's too late.
I think you might be confused.
I was told about the riot and came here
to protect these priceless magic tools.
You can drop the act now.
What did you do to Deed's wand?
What are you talking about?
His wand was fine. I checked.
And everyone believed you.
Because you're a magic tool specialist.
It's your job to inspect
and maintain all the tools.
So it'd be pretty easy for
you to rig Deed's wand to
discharge on its own and to
eliminate evidence of tampering.
Child's play, really.
And it wasn't just that incident.
You've been encouraging animosity between
nobles and commoners this whole time.
Once the rioters overran the school,
you were planning to ring that
bell and make monsters attack.
Am I right?
Or am I right?
Well, that's a fascinating hypothesis,
but do you have evidence to back it up?
No, none at all.
But proof or not, I know everything.
For example, I know the commoner
movement means nothing to you.
Let's assume what you're
saying is correct.
What sort of motive would
I have to do any of it?
He has a point.
The kingdom relies on
the Oruso Company for
the mining and distribution
of magic stones.
and they've accumulated
massive wealth from it.
If they were to dismantle the
system that gave them their riches,
they'd be left with nothing.
There's only one reason
he'd take such a risk.
They're using Linnaeus as
a hostage, aren't they?
I know about that, too.
She's more than just your sister.
She's someone you love very much.
What does that mean?
Ray Taylor, tell me what you know.
Can you believe that some would say
homosexuality is the forbidden love,
but here you are with Lene and she's
your blood sibling and you - Stop it!
Don't say another word!
Please, Ray!
Just stop! Lene, don't!
Don't do it!
Promise you won't get in my brother's way!
I don't...
I don't want to hurt
Miss Claire, but I will!
It's such a shame, Lene.
Master Lambert, please stop this.
I promise you I'll do
something to help Lene.
You can.
Master Lambert!
You don't know how terrifying he is.
If I fail, you'll kill Lene
without a moment's hesitation.
I mean it, Ray!
I just can't sleep in peace, can I?
Miss Claire!
Lene?
I'm sure I don't know the full story here,
but tell me, is it accurate to say
that you two are behind all of this?
Surrender now while you have the chance.
I don't care what you were planning to do.
This is where it ends.
Is it now?
I'm afraid that won't do it all.
Whatever's going on right now,
it isn't a plotline in the game.
I don't recognize any of this.
Who is he?
Now, Lambert, be a good
boy and call the monster.
The bell is broken.
Not a problem.
All better now.
As long as you hold up
your end of the bargain,
I'll help you escape the
country as I promised.
Then you and your sister can live
a new life with new identities.
You two could finally have the
life you've always dreamed of.
Go on.
Lambert, wait!
You don't have to do this!
You want that freedom, don't you?
What would it be like not to
hide your love any longer?
I'm sorry, Miss Claire.
Please forgive me.
But it's too late.
We can't go back now!
Is that a chimera?
I'm waiting.
Chimera!
I command you to eliminate the nobles!
Come on, Miss Claire.
We need backup.
Let's go find the guards.
No.
What do you mean? No.
Retreating may mean more casualties and
harsher punishment for Linnaeus and Lambert.
We'll just have to hold it here.
Linnaeus is my responsibility.
She belongs to me!
Responsibility, let's call it that.
You're such a tsundere!
What on earth is a
tsundere and why am I one?
We're at a disadvantage in here.
We need to go somewhere else.
You just blatantly ignored me!
Ms. Clare!
And she sticks to landing!
Sub-Zero, freeze!
Those magic skills of yours
are completely ridiculous.
There's no magic too ridiculous
for a lady ridiculously in love.
Really? Now?
It possesses multiple attributes.
A head of fire, a body of
earth, and a tail of water.
I'm guessing it'll break
out of the ice pretty soon.
Do you know what that means, Miss Claire?
You and I are about to undertake
our first Herculean labor of love.
Haha!
You can't believe I'm so happy.
I want you to be just happy.
I'm not sure if I want you.
You can't believe I'm excellent.
I want you to be happy.
I want you to be a joy.
I want you to be beautiful. I
want you to reach the words.
I want you to be so happy?
Thank you
so
much for watching.
It's like that.
It's not a bad thing, so...
Because when I see my soul,
I won't be able to meet.
I'll be back with it.
I can't see how it will be.
Yes, as long as I have you,
nothing can scare me. Good.
Then let's do this.